Komal Shah

Mobile +918052202672 Address- 402 B – Wing Sahaj Sapphire

E-Mail <u>agarwalkomal89@gmail.com</u> New Vasna Near G.B Shah College

Ahmedabad

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Profile: A Young, Dynamic and Dedicated sales professional with more than 4 years of business experience with demonstrated leadership skills aimed at exceeding sales goals. Proven success in managing sales campaigns with a view to increasing customer base and boosting profits. Well-organized with great attention to detail aimed at executing sales programs in conjunction with set company directives.

Professional Goals include seeking an environment where my knowledge and experience can be shared and enriched to serve the Organization. Secure a challenging role in an organization that offers me opportunity to learn continuously and deliver best results to evolve myself not only as a better professional but also as a better individual.

EDUCATION					
Degree/ Class	Stream	Institution	Board/ University	Percentage	Year of Passing
B.Sc.	Physics, Chemistry, Math	Khalsa Girls Degree College	C.S.J.M. University	54%	2011
Class XII	Physics, Chemistry, Math	S.N.Sen Girls College	U.P. board(State)	52%	2007
Class X	Physics, Chemistry , Math	S.N.Sen Girls College	U.P. board(State)	52%	2005

EXPERIENCE

VC ERP Consulting (Aug 2016 - Till Now) VC ERP Consulting, is a global SAP Consulting company. Experienced with esteemed clientele all over the sphere with 15 years of SAP expertise.

Roles & Responsibilities: Business Development Executive

- Planning and delivering CRM strategies across the company encouraging customer retention and customer Loyalty.
- Working closely with all departments to ensure the CRM works effectively for all aspects of the company
- > Deciding on the CRM platform structure and architecture ensuring it works seamlessly across the organization and captures all required information at key points in the customer life cycle.
- > Identifying new sales leads for SAP Business One.
- > Handling marketing activities such as Events
- > Team Co-ordination and mentoring to college Interns.
- Coordinating with top management (CFO, IT Heads, Board Directors)
- SAP AMS Support

Mindquad Solution Pvt Ltd (Jan 2016- Till Now) MindQuad Solutions Private Limited is multi-competency, enterprise solutions provider based in Ahmedabad, India. As a Microsoft Dynamics solution Provider, They are focused in delivering ERP solutions on Microsoft Dynamics NAV (formerly known as Navision).

Roles & Responsibilities: Business Development Executive

- Identifying new sales leads
- Pitching products and/or services
- Maintaining fruitful relationships with existing customers
- Researching organizations and individuals online (especially on social media) to identify new leads and potential new markets
- Researching the needs of other companies and learning who makes decisions about purchasing
- Contacting potential clients via email or phone to establish rapport and set up meetings
- Planning and overseeing new marketing initiatives
- Attending conferences, meetings and industry events
- Negotiating and renegotiating by phone, email and in person
- Developing sales goals for the team and ensuring they are met
- Training personnel and helping team members develop their skills

VLCC (Oct 2014 – Dec 2014): VLCC is widely recognized for its scientific weight loss solutions and its therapeutic approach to beauty treatments. VLCC is the largest and most-preferred brand in the Wellness domain in the countries it operates in.

Roles & Responsibilities: Guest Relationship Executive

- > Ensure outstanding customer satisfaction by maintaining strong working relationships
- Coordinate and organize Events
- Assisting with all aspects of administrative management, directory maintenance, logistics, equipment inventory and storage
- Ensure that front office staff is available at all the times for customer assistance.
- Follow and enforce established policies and procedures.
- Assist sales team in business acquisitions, planning, retention and management.
- Escalate unresolved guest issues to Director for immediate resolution
- Coordinating between departments and operating units in resolving day-to-day administrative and operational problems.

Dataman Computer Systems (P) Ltd. (Sept 2012 – Sept 2014): A Kanpur based organization, deals in various software solutions to almost every sector including Fashion, Real Estate, Banking, hospitality, Academics, pharmaceuticals, E-Commerce etc.

Roles & Responsibilities: Font Desk/reception (Sept 2013 – June2013):

- > I was responsible for all the work entitled to the reception of a software company.
- Managing EPABX.
- Answer visitor inquiries about the company
- Sort mails, answer incoming calls, and arrange appointments
- Address visitors to appropriate contacts
- Controlling of inward and outward material

Roles & Responsibilities: Tele caller for Marketing (July 2013 – Sept 2014):

- Make cold calls and generate leads.
- > I was able to meet my daily call targets with positive outcomes with the help of my convincing skills.
- Reporting daily activities to seniors.
- Daily Follow ups with customers and sales team
- Data management

ABILITES

- > Proficient in organizing events
- Skilled enough to manage administration
- Good convincing power
- Strong analytical and Interpersonal skills
- Positive thinking.
- Honesty.
- Dedication in job
- Strong communication and IT fluency
- The ability to handle pressure and meet deadlines

SKILLS

- Computer Basics.
- MS-Office, Internet.
- Operating System Windows XP, Vista and 7.,8,10
- ➤ EPABX

INTEREST & ACTIVITIES

- Reading Books
- Internet Surfing.
- Cooking

PERSONAL PROFILE

Husband Name : Mr. Niket Shah

Date of Birth : 02nd June, 1989

Marital Status : Married

Gender : Female

Languages Known : Hindi & English

Nationality : Indian

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above information given by me is true & correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Ahmedabad KOMAL SHAH

Date: 24- Aug-2017